# Vishwas Bhondivale

- **\( +91 9372329334**
- vishwasbhondivale@gmail.com
- Mumbai

https://www.linkedin.com/in/vi shwas bhondivale-5b1a1a228

#### SUMMARY

I'm dedicated IT professional with a B.Sc. in IT from Mumbai University, possess hands-on experience and a strong passion for driving excellence in IT Service Management, and work with an organization where I can apply my thoughts, and skills which will be beneficial for an organization to grow. Recent graduate with excellent research, technical, problem-solving skills and the ability to learn new concepts quickly.

## **PROJECTS**

TMDB APP - DART, FLUTTER

PORTFOLIO - HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### Dreamkasper

Jan 2023 - Present **Front End Intern** 

- · Designing, developing, testing, maintaining, and deploying software in the Flutter framework and Dart
- Communicating with product and engineering leads to implement business and project objectives.

#### **OCTANET**

#### Web Developer Intern

Dec 2023 - Jan 2024

- Writing well designed, testable, efficient code by using best software development practices
- Creating website layout/user interfaces by using standard HTML/CSS practices
- Integrating data from various back-end services and databases

**FORTUNE** 

Sales Executive

Jan 2023 - Oct 2023

# **EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS**

# **BACHELOR OF SCIENCE - INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY**

K.V.Pendharkar College of Arts Commerce & Science - University of Mumbai Completed BSc-IT Degree with 7.85 CGPA

## HIGHER SECONDARY EDUCATION

K.V.Pendharkar College of Arts Commerce & Science - University of Mumbai Completed HSC in 2018 with 60%

## SECONDARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATE

Swami Vivekanand Vidhya mandir dom(east) Completed SSC in 2016 with 70%

### **SKILL**

- DART
- HTML
- FLUTTER
- CSS
- SQLite
- JAVASRIPT
- Firebase
- Rest Api
- Git
- · Good communication skill
- · Able to work in a team
- Great problem solving skill
- Technical Skills
- · Completed Certification in PLSQL/MySQL